Guide to the Sports Information Office Records, 1932-ongoing UA.13.02.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Sports Information Office records
1932-ongoing
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Duke University. Sports Information Office
UA.13.02.0001
320 Linear Feet
The Sports Information Office provides information about Duke athletics to the media. They also facilitate press interviews with Duke athletes and coaches. The collection contains press releases, photographs, audio reels, and other material pertaining to sports at Duke University. The date ranges from 1932-ongoing.
Access Restrictions
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48-hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Use of audiotapes and videotapes from this collection requires the creation of reference copies. Reference copies for some materials may have been made, and if a reference copy exists, it is noted in this finding aid. To arrange for the creation of reference copies of other items, please contact University Archives staff. Although these recordings are now stored in a stable environment, their condition and playback quality is unknown.
Portions of this collection are unprocessed and may require the assistance of University Archives Staff.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The Sports Information Office records were received by the University Archives as a transfer over time.
Historical Note
The Sports Information Office provides information about Duke athletics to the media. They also facilitate press interviews with Duke athletes and coaches. For many years, the Sports Information Office has maintained records, photographs and other material about Duke athletic teams.
Collection Overview
This collection includes press releases, photographs, clippings, scrapbooks, plaques, audio reels and other material pertaining to sports at Duke University. Topics range from individual sports (badminton, boxing, high school basketball) and the coaching school to freshmen sports. For ease of patron use, individual collections have been created for the bulk of sport-specific information. For example, there is a separate finding aid for both men and women's basketball, football, and baseball. Please see the list of Related Collections below for a comprehensive list. The collection ranges in date from 1932-ongoing.
Accessions after 2012 have been added as separate series. These accessions include materials on the Men's Basketball Championships in 1991, 1992, 2001, 2010, and 2015, as well as many other materials covering athletics at Duke.
Related Material
Baseball Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University. Cross Country and Track and Field Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University. Fencing Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University. Field Hockey Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University. Football Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University. Golf Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University. Gymnastics Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University. Lacrosse Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University. Men's Basketball Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University. Rowing Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University. Soccer Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University. Swimming and Diving Team Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University. Tennis Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University. Volleyball Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University. Women's Basketball Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University. Wrestling Records, Duke University Archives, David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University.
Duke University -- Sports; Duke University. Sports Information Office
- General Files, 1932-1991, 6 boxes
  Scope and Contents note
  This series includes general files created by the Sports Information Office. It includes largely press releases but also clippings and files on high school basketball.
  - Badminton Championships Program, Cameron Indoor Stadium, April 1942 (Box 1)
  - Badminton National championships, 1942 (Box 1)
  - Boxing, 1932-1936 (Box 1)
  - Boxing, 1937-1940 (Box 1)
  - Charlotte Feature on Simons, Muse, and Chapman, 1946 (Box 1)
  - Coaching School, 1932-1935 (Box 1)
  - Coaching School, 1936-1940 (Box 1)
  - Composite spring Sports Schedules and Releases, 1956-1973 (17 folders) (Box 1)
  - Director: Correspondence, circa 1942-1943 (Box 1)
  - Football: General Stories, early 1940s (Box 1)
  - Freshmen Sports, 1933-1935 (Box 2)
  - Freshmen Sports, 1936-1939 (Box 2)
  - Freshmen Sports, 1948-1951 (Box 2)
  - Faculty Softball, 1933, 1949, undated (Box 2)
  - Intramurals, 1932-1947 (Box 2A)
  - Register and Press Releases, 1933-1935 (Box 2A)
  - Register and Press Releases, 1936-1939 (Box 2A)
  - Register and Press Releases, 1939-1943 (Box 3)
  - Register and Press Releases, 1946-1949 (Box 3)
  - Spring Sports/Press Releases, 1950 (Box 3)
  - Spring Sports/Press Releases, 1954 (Box 3)
  - Spring Sports/Press Releases, 1955 (Box 3)
  - Press Releases, 1973 May-Dec. (Box 3)
  - Press Releases, 1974 Jan.-Dec. (Box 3)
  - Press Releases, 1975 Jan.-Dec. (Box 3)
  - Press Releases, 1976 Jan.-Dec. (Box 3)
  - Press Releases, 1977 Jan.-Dec. (Box 3)
  - Press Releases, 1978 Jan.-June (Box 3)
  - Press Releases, 1978 July-Dec. (Box 4)
  - Press Releases, 1979 Jan.-June (Box 4)
  - Press Releases, 1979 July-Dec. (Box 4)
  - Press Releases, 1980 Jan.-June (Box 4)
  - Press Releases, 1980 July-Dec. (Box 4)
  - Press Releases, 1981 Jan.-June (Box 4)
  - Press Releases, 1981 July-Dec. (Box 4)
  - Press Releases, 1982 Jan.-Dec. (Box 4)
  - Press Releases, 1983 (Box 4)
  - Press Releases, 1984 (Box 4)
  - Press Releases, 1985 (Box 4)
  - Press Releases, 1986 (Box 4)
  - Press Releases, 1987 (Box 4)
  - Press Releases, 1988 (Box 5)
  - Press Releases, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Press Releases, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Press Releases, 1991 (Box 5)
  - Southern High School Basketball Tournament, 1939-1946 (Box 5)
  - Southern High School, N.C. State High School Basketball Tournaments, circa 1940s (Box 5)
  - A Story of Glory, Ted Mann: Notes, correspondence, clippings (2 folders) (Box 5)
  - A Story of Glory, Final Manuscript (3 folders) (Box 6)
  - Summer School Sports, 1935; undated (Box 6)
  - Summaries and Miscellaneous, 1932-1934 (Box 6)
  - Track-Lacrosse-Crew, pre-1980 (Box 6)
  - Women's Athletics, 1973-1976 (Box 6)
  - Women's Schedules and Intercollegiates, pre-1980 (Box 6)
- Memorabilia and Oversize Material (including oversize photographs), 1937-1995, 5 boxes
  This series contains oversize photograhs (some of which are mounted), oversize printed material, plaques, and scrapbooks.
  - Hall of Fame Bowl Plaque, 1995 (Box 7)
  - Color photograph from The Herald Sun of "The Shot," Basketball, 1992 (Box 7)
  - Final Four Minneapolis Pins (2), 1992 (Box 7)
  - Lacrosse, vol. 9, no. 2 (Jack Persons article), 1985 April (Box 7)
  - Signed broadside of Ben Bennett's ACC Record, circa 1983 (Box 7)
  - Facsimile of basketball team caricatures, undated (Box 7)
  - NCAA Basketball Media information, 1986 (Box 7)
  - World Top 20 Poll plaque, 1979 Dec. 17 (Box 7)
  - Ed Koffenberger, All-American, unmounted image, 1947 (Box 8)
  - Mounted images of the following All-American basketball players:
    - Ed Koffenberger (1946, 1947) (Box 8)
    - Dick Groat (1951, 1952) (Box 8)
    - Jeff Mullins (1964) (Box 8)
    - Jack Marin (1966) (Box 8)
    - Bob Verga (1966, 1967) (Box 8)
    - Mike Lewis (1968) (Box 8)
  - All-American certificates for baseball players:
    - Dick Groat (1952) (Box 8)
    - William Werber, Jr. (1952, 1954) (Box 8)
    - Albert Spangler (1954) (Box 8)
  - Oversize images of All-American football players and superlatives
    - Woody Lipscomb (1937) (Box 8)
    - Dan Hill, Jr. (1938) (Box 8)
    - Pat Preston (1943) (Box 8)
    - Bill Millner (1943, 1946) (Box 8)
    - Billy Cox (1950) (Box 8)
    - Jack Kistler (1951) (Box 8)
    - Red Smith (1951) (Box 8)
    - Dwight Bumgarner (1960) (Box 8)
    - Jean Berry (1962 (Box 8)
    - Jean Berry (1962) and Jay Wilkinson (1963) (Box 8)
    - Bob Matheson (1966) (Box 8)
  - AACBC District 3 Champs plaque, 1961 (Box 9 (Heavy box))
  - Art Gregory, Order of the Ahepa Athletic Hall of Fame plaque, 1981 (Box 9 (Heavy box))
  - Eddie Cameron resolution, 1972 (Box 9 (Heavy box))
  - Big Four Basketball Tournament Champs plaque, 1979-1980 (Box 9 (Heavy box))
  - Stanley Schneider and Leonard Merl plaque, early 1980s (Box 9 (Heavy box))
  - Rose Bowl Scrapbook, 1942 (Box 10)
  - Scrapbook - Football, 1970; Basketball, 1970-1971 (Box 11)
- Media Guides and Publicity 1985-2000, 6 boxes
  - Fencing (Box 12)
  - Men's Swimming (Box 12)
  - Women's Swimming (Box 12)
  - Men's Tennis (Box 12)
  - Rowing (Box 12)
  - Women's Lacrosse (Box 13)
  - Men's Soccer (Box 14)
  - Men's Golf (Box 15)
  - Track and Field (Men and Women) (Box 15)
  - Women's Soccer (Box 15)
  - Baseball (Box 15)
  - Misc./General (Box 16)
  - Women's Tennis (Box 16)
  - Wrestling (Box 16)
  - Field Hockey (Box 16)
  - Men's Lacrosse (Box 16)
  - Volleyball (Box 17)
  - Women's Golf (Box 17)
- Sound Recordings, 1982-1985, undated, 5 boxes
  This series contains radio station broadcasts of Duke University football and basketball games recorded on 1/4 tape on 10-inch reels. Not all reels are labeled and not all distinguish between football and basketball.
  - Unlabeled, 1982 July 19 (Box 18)
  - Duke/Tennessee, 1982 Sept. 4 (Box 18)
  - Duke/Navy, 1982 Sept. 19 (2 reels) (Box 18)
  - Duke/Clemson, 1982 Oct. 16 (Box 18)
  - Duke/UNC, 1982 Nov. (2 reels) (Box 18)
  - Duke/ECU, 1982 Nov. 27 (Box 18)
  - Duke/Appalachian State, 1982 Nov. 30 (Box 18)
  - Duke/Colorado, 1982 Dec. 2 (Box 18)
  - Duke/Virginia, 1982 Dec. 8 (Box 18)
  - Duke/New Hampshire, 1982 Dec. 29 (Box 18)
  - Duke/Wagner, 1983 Jan. 5 (Box 18)
  - Duke/Lasalle, 1983 Jan. 8 (Box 18)
  - Duke/Louisville, 1983 Jan. 12 (Box 19)
  - Duke/Maryland, 1983 Jan. 15 (Box 19)
  - Duke/Wake Forest, 1983 Jan. 19 (Box 19)
  - Duke/UNC, 1983 Jan. 22 (Box 19)
  - Duke/NC State, 1983 Jan. 26 (Box 19)
  - Duke/William & Mary, 1983 Feb. 2 (Box 19)
  - Duke/Georgia Tech, 1983 Feb. 9 (Box 19)
  - Duke/Stetson, 1983 Feb. 16 (Box 19)
  - Duke/Wake Forest, 1983 Feb. 19 (Box 19)
  - Duke/Maryland, 1983 Feb. 21 (Box 19)
  - Duke/NC State, 1983 Feb. 23 (Box 19)
  - Unlabeled, 1983 Feb. 26 (Box 19)
  - Duke/Clemson, 1983 March 2 (Box 19)
  - Duke/UNC, 1983 March 5 (2 reels) (Box 20)
  - ACC Tournament: First half of NC State/Wake Forest, 1983 March 11 (Box 20)
  - ACC Tournament: Second half of NC State/Wake Forest; part of Duke/Virginia, 1983 March 11 (Box 20)
  - ACC Tournament: End of Duke/Virginia; all of Maryland/Georgia Tech, 1983 March 11 (Box 20)
  - Duke/Indiana, 1984 Sept. 8 (2 reels) (Box 20)
  - Duke/Army, 1984 Sept. 29 (Box 20)
  - Duke/Virginia, 1984 Oct. 6 (Box 20)
  - Duke/Virginia Tech, 1984 Oct. 13 (Box 20)
  - Duke/Clemson, 1984 Oct. 20 (Box 20)
  - Duke/Maryland, 1984 Oct. 27 (Box 20)
  - Duke/Georgia Tech, 1984 Nov. 3 (Box 20)
  - Duke/Athletes in Action, 1984 Nov. 14 (Box 21)
  - Duke/NCSU (football), 1984 Nov. 17 (Box 21)
  - Duke/UNC (football), 1984 Nov. 24 (Box 21)
  - Duke/St. Louis, 1984 Nov. 26 (Box 21)
  - Duke/William & Mary, 1984 Nov. 28 (Box 21)
  - Duke/Appalachian State, 1984 Dec. 5 (Box 21)
  - Duke/Virginia, 1984 Dec. 8 (Box 21)
  - Duke/Davidson, 1984 Dec. 17 (Box 21)
  - Duke/Southwestern, 1984 Dec. 19 (Box 21)
  - Duke/Univ. of Alabama-Birmingham, 1984 Dec. 28 (Box 21)
  - Duke/Southern California, 1984 Dec. 29 (Box 21)
  - Duke/Virginia, 1985 Jan. 5 (Box 21)
  - Duke/Wake Forest, 1985, Nov. 10 (Box 21)
  - Duke/Wake Forest, undated (Box 22)
  - Georgia Tech/Virginia, undated (Box 22)
  - UNC/NC State, undated (Box 22)
  - Virginia/NC State, undated (Box 22)
  - Unlabeled, undated (Box 22)
  - Unlabeled, undated (Box 22)
  - Unlabeled, undated (Box 22)
  - Unlabeled, undated (Box 22)
  - Unlabeled, undated (Box 22)
  - Unlabeled, undated (Box 22)
  - Unlabeled, undated (Box 22)
  - Unlabeled, undated (Box 22)
  - Duke/Colorado, reel 2, undated (Box 22)
- UA2013-0034, 1967-2013; 5
  Scope and Contents
  This accession contains a large amount of material covering several decades and multiple sports, and includes clippings and other materials related to the 1991, 1992, and 2001 Men's Basketball Championships, as well as many individual player files. A more detailed inventory of some boxes is available.
  - Men's Lacrosse, Wrestling, Men's Soccer, Men's Baseball, 2001-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.1)
  - Women's Golf, Women's Soccer, Women's Basketball, 2007-2012 (Box UA2013-0034.2)
  - Wrestling, Swimming and Diving, Men's Soccer, Women's Field Hockey, 2001-2002 (Box UA2013-0034.3)
  - Swimming and Diving, Men's Baseball, Men's Football, 2000-2011 (Box UA2013-0034.4)
  - Negatives and Prints, Men's Basketball, 1990-1992 (Box UA2013-0034.5)
  - Women's Basketball, Women's Soccer, Women's Golf, 2008-2012 (Box UA2013-0034.6)
  - Women's Basketball, Track and Field, Cross Country, 1998-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.7)
  - Track and Field, Cross Country, Men's Lacrosse, Wrestling, 2001-2003 (Box UA2013-0034.8)
  - Wrestling Media Guides, 1967-2008 (Box UA2013-0034.9)
  - Wrestling, 1990-1997 (Box UA2013-0034.10)
  - Wrestling, 2003-2007 (Box UA2013-0034.11)
  - Wrestling Harvey History (Box UA2013-0034.12)
  - Wrestling Harvey History (Box UA2013-0034.13)
  - Wrestling Harvey History (Box UA2013-0034.14)
  - Football photos, Wrestling Harvey History (Box UA2013-0034.15)
  - Wrestling Score Books (Box UA2013-0034.16)
  - Wrestling, Cross Country, Track and Field, Football, 1985-2008 (Box UA2013-0034.17)
  - Football yearbook, Women's Basketball photos (Box UA2013-0034.18)
  - Duke Weekly - Bound, 2002-2008 (Box UA2013-0034.19)
  - Photos, various, unlabled (Box UA2013-0034.20)
  - Cross Country, Football, Basketball, Unfoldered assorted (Box UA2013-0034.21)
  - Assorted Files, Baseball, Men's Lacrosse, Basketball, 1991-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.22)
  - Swimming and Diving, Men's Basketball, Unfoldered Assorted, 1991-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.23)
  - Men's Basketball, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.24)
  - Women's Basketball, 2013 (Box UA2013-0034.25)
  - Men's Basketball, 2013 (Box UA2013-0034.26)
  - Blue Devil Weekly, 1996-2001 (Box UA2013-0034.27)
  - Blue Devil Weekly, 1993-1996 (Box UA2013-0034.28)
  - Individual player files and photos, Women's Basketball clippings, games, 2012 (Box UA2013-0034.29)
  - Women's Basketball, Women's Tennis, 2010-2012 (Box UA2013-0034.30)
  - Rowing, Volleyball, Baseball, Fencing, 2006-2009 (Box UA2013-0034.31)
  - Football, 2011 (Box UA2013-0034.32)
  - Football, 2011-2012 (Box UA2013-0034.33)
  - Football, 1996-2012 (Box UA2013-0034.34)
  - Football, 1987-1996 (Box UA2013-0034.35)
  - Football, 1986-2007 (Box UA2013-0034.36)
  - Football, 2007 (Box UA2013-0034.37)
  - Football, 2006-2007 (Box UA2013-0034.38)
  - Football, 2005-2006 (Box UA2013-0034.39)
  - Football, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.40)
  - Football, 2005 (Box UA2013-0034.41)
  - Football, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.42)
  - Football, 2004 (Box UA2013-0034.43)
  - Baseball, 2002-2003 (Box UA2013-0034.44)
  - Baseball, Football, 2001-2012 (Box UA2013-0034.45)
  - Football, 2009-2012 (Box UA2013-0034.46)
  - Football, 2010 (Box UA2013-0034.47)
  - Football, 2008-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.48)
  - Football, 2008 (Box UA2013-0034.49)
  - Football, 2008-2009 (Box UA2013-0034.50)
  - Football, 2009 (Box UA2013-0034.51)
  - Football, Baseball, 2004-2009 (Box UA2013-0034.52)
  - Field Hockey, 2004-2011 (Box UA2013-0034.53)
  - Field Hockey, Golf, 2003-2012 (Box UA2013-0034.54)
  - Men's Golf, 2003-2009 (Box UA2013-0034.55)
  - Men's Golf, Women's Golf, 2001-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.56)
  - Women's Golf, 2003-2004 (Box UA2013-0034.57)
  - Women's Golf, 2001-2003 (Box UA2013-0034.58)
  - Men's Lacrosse, 2010-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.59)
  - Men's Lacrosse, 2009-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.60)
  - Men's Lacrosse, 2007-2008 (Box UA2013-0034.61)
  - Men's Lacrosse, 2006 (Box UA2013-0034.62)
  - Men's Lacrosse, Women's Lacrosse, 2003-2012 (Box UA2013-0034.63)
  - Women's Lacrosse, 2006-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.64)
  - Men's Lacrosse, Women's Lacrosse, 2003-2007 (Box UA2013-0034.65)
  - Men's Lacrosse, Field Hockey, 2006-2007 (Box UA2013-0034.66)
  - Women's Rowing, Women's and Men's rowing, Field Hockey, 2002-2008 (Box UA2013-0034.67)
  - Rowing, Men's Soccer, 2000-2012 (Box UA2013-0034.68)
  - Football, 2003-2004 (Box UA2013-0034.69)
  - Football, 2003-2004 (Box UA2013-0034.70)
  - Football, Men's Soccer, 2003-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.71)
  - Men's Soccer, 2006-2009 (Box UA2013-0034.72)
  - Men's Soccer, Women's Soccer, 2003-2008 (Box UA2013-0034.73)
  - Women's Soccer, 2002-2005 (Box UA2013-0034.74)
  - Women's Soccer, Swimming and Diving, 2001-2012 (Box UA2013-0034.75)
  - Swimming and Diving, 2004-2007 (Box UA2013-0034.76)
  - Swimming and Diving, Men's Tennis, 2002-2012 (Box UA2013-0034.77)
  - Men's Tennis, 2003-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.78)
  - Men's Tennis, Women's Tennis, 2002-2012 (Box UA2013-0034.79)
  - Women's Tennis, 2002-2007 (Box UA2013-0034.80)
  - Women's Tennis, Track and Field, 2003-2010 (Box UA2013-0034.81)
  - Track and Field, Cross Country, 2003-2007 (Box UA2013-0034.82)
  - Cross Country, Track and Field, 2005-2006 (Box UA2013-0034.83)
  - Track and Field, Volleyball, 2002-2005 (Box UA2013-0034.84)
  - Volleyball, Wrestling, 2002-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.85)
  - Volleyball, Wrestling, 2002-2013 (Box UA2013-0034.86)
  - Volleyball, Hall of Fame, 1987-2006 (Box UA2013-0034.87)
  - Hall of Fame, Letter, 1965-2007 (Box UA2013-0034.88)
  - Hall of Fame, Letter, Historical Files, 1970-2002 (Box UA2013-0034.89)
  - Historical Files, Basketball, Football, 1965-2002 (Box UA2013-0034.90)
  - Historical Files, Track, Football, ?-1996 (Box UA2013-0034.91)
  - Historical Files, Football, Lacrosse, Golf, 1990-2001 (Box UA2013-0034.92)
  - Historical Files, Track, Band, Mascot, Cheerleaders, World War II, ?-1998 (Box UA2013-0034.93)
  - Historical Miscellaneous Files, 1990-2012 (Box UA2013-0034.94)
  - Historical Miscellaneous Files, Women's Basketball, ?-2004 (Box UA2013-0034.95)
  - Women's Basketball, 2002-2004 (Box UA2013-0034.96)
  - Women's Basketball, 2002-2004 (Box UA2013-0034.97)
  - Women's Basketball, 2003-2004 (Box UA2013-0034.98)
  - Women's Basketball, 2002-2003 (Box UA2013-0034.99)
  - Women's Basketball, 2002-2003 (Box UA2013-0034.100)
  - Women's Basketball, 1990-2005 (Box UA2013-0034.101)
  - Women's Basketball, 2000-2005 (Box UA2013-0034.102)
  - Women's Basketball, 1986-2000 (Box UA2013-0034.103)
  - Women's Basketball, 2006-2007 (Box UA2013-0034.104)
  - Women's Basketball, 2006-2007 (Box UA2013-0034.105)
  - Women's Basketball, 2004-2007 (Box UA2013-0034.106)
  - Women's Basketball, 2004-2005 (Box UA2013-0034.107)
  - Women's Basketball, 2004-2006 (Box UA2013-0034.108)
  - Women's Basketball, 2005-2006 (Box UA2013-0034.109)
  - Women's Basketball, 2005-2006 (Box UA2013-0034.110)
  - Women's Basketball, 2007-2008 (Box UA2013-0034.111)
  - Women's Basketball, 2007-2008 (Box UA2013-0034.112)
  - Women's Basketball, 2007-2009 (Box UA2013-0034.113)
  - Women's Basketball, 2008-2009 (Box UA2013-0034.114)
  - Women's Basketball, 2009-2011 (Box UA2013-0034.115)
  - Women's Basketball, 2010-2011 (Box UA2013-0034.116)
  - Women's Basketball, Player Files Ab-Al (Box UA2013-0034.117)
  - Player Files Al-Ay (Box UA2013-0034.118)
  - Player Files Ay-Ba (Box UA2013-0034.119)
  - Player Files Ba-Be (Box UA2013-0034.120)
  - Player Files Be-Be (Box UA2013-0034.121)
  - Player Files Be-Bl (Box UA2013-0034.122)
  - Player Files Bl-Bo (Box UA2013-0034.123)
  - Player Files Bo-Br (Box UA2013-0034.124)
  - Player Files Br-Bu (Box UA2013-0034.125)
  - Player Files Bu-Bu (Box UA2013-0034.126)
  - Player Files Ca-Ca (Box UA2013-0034.127)
  - Player Files Ca-Ch (Box UA2013-0034.128)
  - Player Files Ch-Cl (Box UA2013-0034.129)
  - Player Files Cl-Co (Box UA2013-0034.130)
  - Player Files Co-Cu (Box UA2013-0034.131)
  - Player Files Cu-Da (Box UA2013-0034.132)
  - Player Files Da-Da (Box UA2013-0034.133)
  - Player Files Da-Di (Box UA2013-0034.134)
  - Player Files Di-Du (Box UA2013-0034.135)
  - Player Files Du-Dy (Box UA2013-0034.136)
  - Player Files Ea-Fa (Box UA2013-0034.137)
  - Player Files Fa-Fi (Box UA2013-0034.138)
  - Player Files Fi-Fo (Box UA2013-0034.139)
  - Player Files Fr-Ga (Box UA2013-0034.140)
  - Player Files Ga-Go (Box UA2013-0034.141)
  - Player Files Go-Gr (Box UA2013-0034.142)
  - Player Files Gr-Ha (Box UA2013-0034.143)
  - Player Files Ha-Ha (Box UA2013-0034.144)
  - Player Files Ha-He (Box UA2013-0034.145)
  - Player Files He-Hi (Box UA2013-0034.146)
  - Player Files Hi-Ho (Box UA2013-0034.147)
  - Player Files Ho-Hu (Box UA2013-0034.148)
  - Player Files Hu-Ja (Box UA2013-0034.149)
  - Player Files Ja-Jo (Box UA2013-0034.150)
  - Player Files Jo-Ke (Box UA2013-0034.151)
  - Player Files Ke-Ko (Box UA2013-0034.152)
  - Player Files Ko-La (Box UA2013-0034.153)
  - Player Files La-La (Box UA2013-0034.154)
  - Player Files La-Li (Box UA2013-0034.155)
  - Player Files Li-Ma (Box UA2013-0034.156)
  - Player Files Ma-Ma (Box UA2013-0034.157)
  - Player Files Ma-Mc (Box UA2013-0034.158)
  - Player Files Mc-Mc (Box UA2013-0034.159)
  - Player Files Mc-Mi (Box UA2013-0034.160)
  - Player Files Mi-Mo (Box UA2013-0034.161)
  - Player Files Mo-Ne (Box UA2013-0034.162)
  - Player Files Ne-No (Box UA2013-0034.163)
  - Player Files No-Pa (Box UA2013-0034.164)
  - Player Files Pa-Pa (Box UA2013-0034.165)
  - Player Files Pa-Pl (Box UA2013-0034.166)
  - Player Files Pl-Ra (Box UA2013-0034.167)
  - Player Files Ra-Re (Box UA2013-0034.168)
  - Player Files Re-Ro (Box UA2013-0034.169)
  - Player Files Ro-Sa (Box UA2013-0034.170)
  - Player Files Sa-Sc (Box UA2013-0034.171)
  - Player Files Sc-Si (Box UA2013-0034.172)
  - Player Files Si-Sm (Box UA2013-0034.173)
  - Player Files Sm-So (Box UA2013-0034.174)
  - Player Files So-St (Box UA2013-0034.175)
  - Player Files St-Te (Box UA2013-0034.176)
  - Player Files Te-To (Box UA2013-0034.177)
  - Player Files To-Va (Box UA2013-0034.178)
  - Player Files Va-Wa (Box UA2013-0034.179)
  - Player Files Wa-Wa (Box UA2013-0034.180)
  - Player Files Wa-We (Box UA2013-0034.181)
  - Player Files We-Wi (Box UA2013-0034.182)
  - Player Files Wi-Wi (Box UA2013-0034.183)
  - Player Files Wi-Wy (Box UA2013-0034.184)
  - Player Files Ya-Za (Box UA2013-0034.185)
  - Football Slides (Box UA2013-0034.186)
  - Basketball Photos (Box UA2013-0034.187)
  - Basketball Clippings, Krzyzewski (Box UA2013-0034.188)
  - Men's Basketball, 2010-2011 (Box UA2013-0034.189)
  - Men's Basketball, 2010-2011 (Box UA2013-0034.190)
  - Men's Basketball, 2009-2011 (Box UA2013-0034.191)
  - Men's Basketball, 2010-2012 (Box UA2013-0034.192)
  - Men's Basketball, 2011-2012 (Box UA2013-0034.193)
  - Men's Basketball, 2009-2011 (Box UA2013-0034.194)